dealseekingmom.com 2010-12-23

# Privacy Policy

Would you like to have these great bargains delivered right to your inbox? Join over 65,000 fellow deal seekers and [subscribe to Deal Seeking Mom](http://dealseekingmom.com/subscribe-to-the-blog/). Also become a [fan of Deal Seeking Mom](http://facebook.com/dealseekingmom) on Facebook for more conversation, additional deals and a peek at the freebies I receive in the mail. Thanks for visiting!

### **:: Our Commitment to Privacy**

This section summarizes what personally identifiable information Deal Seeking Mom may collect, if any, and how I might use this information. This policy also describes other important topics relating to your privacy. Deal Seeking Mom reserves the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. I will promptly reflect any such modifications in these Web pages.

### **:: Use of Cookies and Web Beacons  
**

Deal Seeking Mom may use cookies to store information about visitors’ preferences or other information that visitors send via their browser.

Some of my advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on my site. My advertising partners include, but are not limited to, Real Girls Media, Google Adsense, and Coupons.com.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks sponsor advertisements and links on Deal Seeking Mom that are sent directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or web beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

Deal Seeking Mom has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt out of certain practices. Deal Seeking Mom’s privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

### **:: Children**

I will not collect any information from children under 18.

### **:: Information Collection**

There are occasions when I will ask for personal information, such as when you enter a giveaway. In these cases, I will only collect personally identifiable information (such as name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) that you voluntarily provide through my Website or via email correspondence.

I will not sell or exchange your personal information at any time. I will collect general information (such as the type of browser you use, the files you request, and the domain name and country from which you request information) to improve my Website and better meet your needs.

### **:: Use of Information**

Before I collect any personally identifiable information, I will provide an explanation for the possible use of your data. For example, the information you supply might be used by Deal Seeking Mom to respond to your inquiries or supply you with requested information. It may be necessary, if required by law or if pertinent to judicial or governmental investigations, to release your personally identifiable information. If you have submitted personal information to me electronically and would like it removed or modified, please contact me. I will use every possible reasonable effort to comply with your request.

### **:: Links**

While Deal Seeking Mom is highly selective about which sites we provide links to, I do not control these web sites, nor do I endorse or otherwise accept responsibility for the content or privacy policies of those sites. I encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on third party sites.

[Disclaimer](http://dealseekingmom.com/disclaimer/) | [Disclosure Policy](http://dealseekingmom.com/disclosure-policy/) | Privacy Policy | [User Agreement](http://dealseekingmom.com/user-agreement/)
